24hgold.com 2018-12-23

# 24hGold - Privacy Policy

24HGOLD PRIVACY POLICY   
---  
**Email Privacy Policy**  
We have created this email privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information.

**Why did you receive an email from us?**  
If you received a mailing from us, (a) your email address is either listed with us as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future ("opt-in"), or (b) you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings.

 **How we protect your privacy**  
We use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system.

 **Personal Information**   
We will never ask you for personal information--your credit card number, for example--except when you place an order. At that time, we will provide a secure (SSL, encrypted) connection and require you to submit only the information needed to complete and fulfill your order. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone, nor share it in any other way, unless required to by a law enforcement agency that takes the proper steps to require it.

**Sharing and Usage**  
We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this Information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you.
